frogads.com 2012-12-30

# Privacy Policy: FrogAds.com

The FrogAds.com Privacy Policy provides information regarding accuracy, access, security and how FrogAds.com controls client information acquired from its Website(s). 

The FrogAds.com Website mission 

The mission of the FrogAds.com Website is to provide clients with the most up-to-date product and company information and present it in a manner best suited to their needs. 

The FrogAds.com Website may be accessed by all Internet users on a 24/7 basis. 

The FrogAds.com Website is the most accurate source of information on FrogAds.com including its products/services. Questions regarding the accuracy of information on the FrogAds.com Website may be directed to Team@FrogAds.com. 

Handling of personal information 

FrogAds.com requests information from clients if they choose to subscribe to email lists, place orders, register for events, register for membership, or if they choose to respond to advertising or promotions. This personal information is necessary in order for FrogAds to fulfill the client's request. 

This information may also be used by FrogAds.com to contact or update the client with periodic FrogAds.com publications, product details or other special offers. FrogAds.com does not allow other companies to offer services or products of value to the client. The client may unsubscribe or request that their information not be shared by directing their request to Team@FrogAds.com. Please provide the exact name and address. In the case of email, only clients who have consented to receive email updates are included on email lists and instructions on how to "unsubscribe" from further solicitations is included in every such email they receive from FrogAds.com. FrogAds.com does not share email addresses with other companies. FrogAds.com does not partner with or have any special relationships with any ad server companies. 

From time to time, FrogAds.com may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If information practices change at some time in the future FrogAds.com will post the policy changes to the FrogAds.com Website to notify the client of these changes and provide instructions to opt-out of these new uses. Clients concerned with how information is used should check back at the FrogAds.com Website periodically. 

FrogAds.com Website management uses IP addresses to diagnose Web server problems and to administrate the FrogAds.com Website. Cookies may be used to store client variables such as member logins across sessions. 

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, FrogAds.com may be contacted at Team@FrogAds.com. 

FrogAds.com is not interested in minors as clients 

FrogAds.com has no desire to collect information from those under the age of 18. In an instance where such information were collected it would be purely accidental and unintentional. FrogAds.com encourages parents to discuss the Internet with their children and monitor personal information that a child may provide via the Internet. 

Unauthorized Use or Abuse of FrogAds.com 

Unauthorized Use or Abuse of FrogAds.com will result in criminal prosecution. This site is exclusively for the use by our customers for the placing of ads for the purpose of advertising, buying, selling, vehicles or related products and services. Please use FrogAds.com responsibly for the benefit of all. 

©2012 FrogAds Inc.   
DBA FrogAds.com All rights reserved.
